<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inspire on Jacob Maestri</title>
    <link>https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Inspire on Jacob Maestri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Professionalism</title>
      <link>https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/professionalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/professionalism/</guid>
      <description>Professionalism#Do I Dress the Part?#I try my best to dress like a used carsales person every day. This means patterned button down, old tie, knock off dress shoes to match. During a pandemic, it also means a mask as well.
There were only three weeks between my college graduation and the first lesson I taught in front of students. It felt like such a rush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformation</title>
      <link>https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/transformation/</guid>
      <description>Transformation#Look Within to be a Better Salesperson#No one ever makes a successful first sale. It takes a while before you learn the trade well enough to be confident in making a sale.
I entered teaching as a fresh college graduate. I lived in a world of round table discussions about post-colonial history and whiteboards with math proofs on them. It was an ideal world, but had little roots in reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobmaestri.com/docs/portfolio/inspire/leadership/</guid>
      <description>Leadership#My Responsiblities Beyond the Dealership#A carsalesman has many responsibilities beyond the dealership. In an ideal world, these extra tasks make you a better salesman.
In my short two years at Byhalia High School, I became the most senior math teacher at the ripe age of 23. I assumed a lot of leadership responsibilities many teachers don&amp;rsquo;t receive until much later in their career. I can definitively say this was not good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
